<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Programming on Codebatik by Aditya</title>
    <link>http://codebatik.com/tags/programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Programming on Codebatik by Aditya</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://codebatik.com/tags/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Love Code</title>
      <link>http://codebatik.com/2017/12/why-i-love-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://codebatik.com/2017/12/why-i-love-code/</guid>
      <description>I always remember when started to write code, it was in high school writing my very first Pascal code and competing with another student to show them that my program was better than theirs. That’s the time I found myself useful and very very exited to finish and gaining the response to my program.
The code was my friend since then. Nothing could make me happier than sitting in front of the monitor through the day in my school lab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Story of Making Url-Shortener as My Side Project</title>
      <link>http://codebatik.com/2017/12/story-of-making-url-shortener-as-my-side-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://codebatik.com/2017/12/story-of-making-url-shortener-as-my-side-project/</guid>
      <description>A few months ago I was thinking about making a simple service that could help me escalate my skill on nodejs. Basicly the service is pretty simple, it&amp;rsquo;s called url-shortener. You just generate a short code and linking with the url, it is simple. That time actually I just thinking to make this simple app with expressing my contribution on open-source project, I never build an open-source project based on NodeJs before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Opinion about Rust and Golang</title>
      <link>http://codebatik.com/2017/11/my-opinion-about-rust-and-golang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://codebatik.com/2017/11/my-opinion-about-rust-and-golang/</guid>
      <description>You know i am really interested with two compiled language which is Rust-lang and Golang from this mid-year of 2017. I think i am are ready to move into more capability which is available on these languages with pretty efficient, fast on managing it&amp;rsquo;s memory and cpu process.
Node.js is cool but instead using a node program to handle some various cpu-intensive or very large memory consumptions around my application. I tend to use a right tool for a right job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mungkin Rust akan Menang</title>
      <link>http://codebatik.com/2017/10/mungkin-rust-akan-menang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 12:05:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://codebatik.com/2017/10/mungkin-rust-akan-menang/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jika kalian jengah mendengar banyak bahasa pemrograman baru yang muncul baru-baru ini, mungkin kali ini saya akan sedikit bercerita. Adalah tentang bahasa pemrograman yang pernah atau sedang saya amati, salah satunya adalah Rust by Mozilla yang mungkin akan banyak berperan di beberapa sektor terutama sistem programming.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Berikan Yang Klien Butuhkan Bukan Yang Diinginkan</title>
      <link>http://codebatik.com/2017/08/berikan-yang-klien-butuhkan-bukan-yang-diinginkan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://codebatik.com/2017/08/berikan-yang-klien-butuhkan-bukan-yang-diinginkan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dalam dunia development seringkali kita dijejali dengan berbagai ucapan klien atau kolega yang menginstruksikan kita untuk membuat sesuatu yang bagus, keren dan menggunakan teknologi paling mutakhir seperti dalam pandangan mereka.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>